Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement by Miku Hatsune
Here we go!
This time, we're joined by Tomozora Niinuma of Tsubaki Factory and
and Momo Kitahara from Ocha no Oma.
This show is about the behind-the-scenes production of the various artists
We'll be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
our recording and rehearsals.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's go behind the scenes with the two MCs.
I'm Shinnuma.
I'm Shinnuma, and the other day, I was at the Nippon Budokan for the graduation performances of our members Riko Yamagishi and Yumeno Kishimoto.
and Yumeno Kishimoto's graduation performance at the Nippon Budokan.
I had a surprise for them there.
There's a song called "A journey to fill what's missing
During the song, each member told the two of us how grateful they are for all we've done for them.
During the song, there was a corner where each member told the two of us how much they appreciated our performance.
I told them "I love you, Rico!
and we all hugged each other.
And it worked!
They were so surprised and happy.
They said they were so surprised and happy.
I'm really glad that it was a success.
I'm glad it was a success, and I'm glad they were happy.
I, Kitahara, was actually there to see it.
Thank you so much!
I cried a lot.
I cried a lot through that performance.
I cried a lot of tears.
I was really moved by the performance.
I was really moved by the performance. I'm just really like thank you for the inspiration.
Thank you so much.
I'm very happy to hear your feedback.
Thank you very much
Yes, I, Kitahara...
The other day, we had our first bus tour in Okayama Prefecture.
Yes, sir.
We had a lot of events such as tangerine picking, barbecue, cruising, and so on.
The mandarin oranges were really sweet and tasty, and the air was really delicious on the cruise.
I was able to experience how delicious the air in Okayama Prefecture is and how nice the nature is, which I usually enjoy in Tokyo.
The bus tour was held in Okayama prefecture because all of us are from different places.
I hope we can do more bus tours in the future.
So I'm getting to be able to talk with them.
We have a lot of events that we can enjoy together, like talking with people who aren't here.
I hope to do it again someday.
Okay, then, let's start with this time's APKAMI.
Tsubaki Factory - If you're just delusional, you're free to be free... Dance Lesson
From the latest single by Tsubaki Factory, here's a dance lesson of "If you're just delusional, you're free!
I'm going to show you how to keep your face and hands in this pose, this pose, this pose, this pose, this pose.
and you've already done it all in that unified way!
5.6.7.8.9.10.11.12.13.14.15.16.17.18.19.20
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
But from 5.6.Seino
But the times, wise gal, they get stronger.
All right!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Okay, okay
It's going to be a pair dance.
The person on the right, please look at me.
Please be the one on the left.Be the one on the left.
Just a minute.
If you're just delusional, you're free.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
One more time...
Ready?
If it's just a fantasy, then you're free
And then...
When you see a heart
Poof, turn inward
Older
Younger
That's right, that's right, that's right.
First, when you're older, the person on the left makes a heart.
And the person on the right
Older
Older.
Older and younger
At this time, make a heart
thumbs in the middle of the heart.
Above the waist, below the waist.
I think it's hard to do if your hands are too far apart.
It's easier if they're closer together.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Let's start with the poses.
Jajajaja jajaja three pose
Five, six, seven, eight.
Dan, dun, dun, dun
That's right, that's right, that's right.
It's pretty hard to exhale here.It's pretty hard to throw up in here.
I'm trying so hard. I'm like, "Chan chan delusional.
I'm trying so hard. Chan-chan delusional.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it fits there
If you're delusional, you're free
I'm strong and a princess
Move to where you were doing this
Move it here at
I'd like to move it to
I'm sorry, but
Kiko and Yumi are pretty far away.
You were off by 0.0% here.
I want to move this the other way.
Yumi, move over here.
Satchan, this way.
No. 2, no. 2, no. 2, no. 2, no. 2, no. 2, no. 2, no. 2.
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Move strong
if you're delusional, dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun
naresama uncle love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love
dun dun dun dun dun dun
Dan, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun
I'll be your teacher, milisee.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Yes, yes, yes, yes! Yes, yes, yes!
I have to be very careful about the fine hand shapes, nuance, and sharpness of this song.
I want you to have a wide stance. I think it would look better if you put your fingers apart a little bit, even though they are very thin and a little higher than your waist.
Yes, yes, yes! And the people in front of me go to the front of their knees, so I think it's easier if I don't spread my toes too wide.
Yes! And one, two, three, four, five.
At this time, don't move your face too much like this.
Boom, boom, boom, boom... It's like a gasp and a look in the eye.
Yes! And from here, Boom! And then 7!
At this time, your right hand should be on this side of your head.
and your left hand presses down on this side of the collarbone.
Right! Seven, eight.
At this point, the right hand goes like this.
And the left hand goes up like this.
Like this!
Like this! Like this!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Seven, eight.
And the people in the back.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
At 5 and 6, here, it's a little bit like slow motion.
It's like, "Ssshhhh, bash out," because it looks pale.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Yeah! And where's the accent here?
Seven, eight in front of you.
Here, very fast.
Seven, ding! It's like...
And the person in the back, five, six, seven, eight...
Here, goomph! And then...
If you make the first movement fast and then slow it down right away, it looks like a buzz, so... If you make the initial movement fast and then slow it down right away, it'll look like a buzz.
It's like a save-ay, not a yes-ay.
Five, six, seven, eight.
The moment you put your hands together, it looks like a "save aye" and a "one.
From "one" to "one".
At the moment of "one", your partner's hands should be at the same height as your partner's.
Make sure that your partner's hands are at the same level as yours at the moment of "one".
Okay, let's try it more carefully.
Please.
Thank you very much.
My favorite maid.
I can't always get around here
No one can reach
You should be happy night
Oh oh oh oh
In front of everyone see clips
I want to fall in love with you
It's like we're always together
You know what I mean?
Every day, every night
I can't do movies
Make up in romance
You're so dazzling
I can't fantasize about Freeland
Starry skies are starry skies
Down down down
I can't fantasize about Freeland
Sweet feeling
The more you laugh at me The more you laugh at me
Make Chew Tea
Love becomes love
I Wanted to Dream
Gray
Ending
I'm Sako Makita, the choreographer.
If it's just my imagination this time, it's a freewheeling choreography.
But there are a lot of detailed hand movements.
There are a lot of hand movements like this.
It's like an image of the world of my fantasy.
The choreography of the chorus is so that you can imitate the choreography with just your hands.
In the chorus of the song, there is a movement that goes along with the lyrics about being older or younger than one's age.
We had a lot of trouble with this part.
I think you can do it after a night's sleep, so please practice if you like!
I think that the song "If you're only delusional, you're free" is very comical and the more you listen to it, the more you'll like it.
This dance was choreographed by Ms. Sako Makita.
She has choreographed many popular songs on TikTok and so on.
We've been uploading videos of us dancing everyday during the release period of this single.
I'd like you to see that too.
I think you can dance to the choreography if you practice enough.
I think you can enjoy the live performance more if you dance with us.
I hope everyone will watch this dance video, learn the choreography, and dance along with me.
I, Kitahara, have this fantasy of freedom.
You know this dance?
I love it, and all the members of Tea Horse dance it!
Really?
I've seen a lot of music videos.
Usually, they're in landscape mode.
but it's a music video with a vertical screen, which was never seen before.It's a music video in portrait mode, which I've never seen before.
I was very happy to be able to see it on a smartphone full of people.
Everyone was a gal, a princess, a prince, or a pajama girl.
or princesses or princes or pajamas or school uniforms.
I was so happy to see all the members in different outfits.
I was so happy to see so many members in different outfits.
I'm listening to Momo-chan's story now
I heard that all the members of Ochanomama are dancing for us.
I'd love to see it on the Tea Horse TikTok account.
I wish they would upload it on their TikTok account.
I'm thinking about it now!
I hope we can dance together someday!
That's all for Tsubaki Factory
If it's just a fantasy, it's a free dance lesson!
See you tomorrow!
This is my account.
Thank you for watching!
Next, here we go!
Morning Musume。23 featuring Mizuki Fukumura
Never Ending Shine Vocal Recording
From Morning Musume。23's latest single
Please take a look at the vocal recording of Mizuki Fukumura of Neverending Shine!
Yes, ma'am.
I like you too much to wonder.
If I had one more person
I'd be able to protect you even more
I love you more than I could ever love you.
I don't know why I love you so much.
I don't want to leave you, I want to be close to you, but if I'm too close, I can't see youI don't want to leave, I want to stay close, too close and I can't see you
This song will be one of my last single songs.
And this song is featuring Mizuki Fukumura, so I'll be singing most of the parts by myself.
I'll be singing most of the parts by myself
I'm going to sing most of the parts by myself, but I've been practicing at home with that in mind
I was practicing at home.
I was practicing at home, thinking about what Mr. Sungkook wanted me to do for this song and what I put into the lyrics.
and what kind of feelings he put into the lyrics.
I was thinking a lot of things.
I was a bit confused about how to express myself.
I think that came out a little in the recording.
No No, right?
Waku-mama's
Hmmm...
No No
Hm...
No
I guess you could say we're all just a bunch of selfish people.
But that's not the point.
If you're selfish, I'll accept it all.
But this feeling is selfishness too
My love...
Not like that... This love...
Nanana...
I'm not going to cry, my feelings are...
cuentos
weier
At first, I was a little lost
I was doing the best I could I was doing the best I could.
I was doing the best I could, but when I imagined singing with everyone
Imagining that I was singing with everyone
I'm glad I was able to do it.
I'm glad.
That's why I'm glad that I was able to express
and what I wanted to express
The feelings that you put into this song
I tried my best to sing the song as it is
I tried my best in this recording.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I, Kitahara, read the liner notes of Mr. Tsunku, who wrote the lyrics to "Never Ending Shine".
I read the liner notes of Mr. Tzunku, who wrote the lyrics to "Never Ending Shine".
I read the liner notes by Mr. Tsunku, who wrote the lyrics and composed the song "Never Ending Shine".
I also read Mr. Fukumura's tips for recording.
I'm very happy to see the video of Mr. Fukumura's recording.
I wanted to listen to it one more time after watching this recording video.
I, Nenuma, really love Morning Musume。 I really love Morning Musume・Musume・Musume・Musume・Musume・Musume
I love Mizuki Fukumura. So when I saw the recording video and the music video, I really felt the graduation.
I feel sad about her graduation, but when I look at the thoughts in the lyrics, I hope she will continue to shine in the future.
I am looking forward to your continued success in the future, and I hope to see you in the future.
I'm looking forward to your continued success, and this video has made me feel that I will always love you.
This was the vocal recording of Morning Musume。 23 featuring Mizuki Fukumura and Never Ending employee Mizuki Fukumura.
Thanks for your work.
Chisora Niinuma of Tsubaki Factory and
Momo Kitahara of Ocha no Oma is presenting Apkami.
Here is the next one!
Makeup lecture by Natsume Nakayama of Ocha-no-Oma
This is Natsume Nakayama of Ocha-no-Oma's makeup class.
This time, she will be doing her usual eye makeup and This time, she shows us the eye makeup she usually does and
and eye makeup for live performances.
Please take a look.
I'm Natsume Nakayama from Ocha-no-Oma, and this time I'd like to show you my usual eye makeup plus eye makeup for live performances.
I'd like to start with the eye makeup and blush.
I'm going to start with the eye makeup that I usually do. I'm using this one, the lightest color that's close to my skin tone.
I'm going to take a brush and blend it with a tissue and then apply it to the inner corner of the eye. The key is to apply it so that the outer corner of the eye is a little bit darker.
Then apply the same color to the crease under the eye.
Use this excess color to connect to the inner corner of the eye.
If you want to make the width of this area narrower, we recommend darkening the tear ducts under the eyes a little to make the width of this area look shorter.
Then, take a thin brush and brush the brown part to the outer part of the black eye.
I'm going to paint from the edge of the eye to the outer edge of the black eye.
This makes the face look clearer.
I often use this method during live performances as well as in everyday life, so I highly recommend it.
Now, the bottom part of the eye is very dark, so I applied it to the crease at the corner of the upper part of the eye.
I'm going to paint the crease where the eyelashes are growing like this.
Take the first brush that you took the color like a light purple pink and apply it to the tear ducts.
Put the color into the tear ducts.
The pink color gives a fragile look to the eyes.
It makes the eyes look more luminous, so I always like to do this a lot.
This is my favorite and I do it often.
I take a slightly lighter shade of the same color and apply it to the double width of the eye.
You can't really tell if there's color or not.
I use the lighter color on top of this to draw the tear troughs.
When you wash your smile, you'll see a line like this.
Aim to draw a line slightly above this line.
If you draw too much, it will be too thick and unnatural.
It is recommended to draw naturally.
Use this to create a three-dimensional effect.
Apply this to the highest part of the eye and the highest part of the tear trough. I will only apply this to the highest point of the eye and the highest point of the tear trough.
If you apply too much, the shadow you just drew will lose its meaning.
So I'm going to apply it to the highest part of the eye like this.
Put it in.
I'm going to do it seriously.
Then you'll get a very plump tear trough.
I would like to do the eyelashes.
I usually use an eyelash curler.
I'm not too particular about it.
I'm not too particular about it, but I just want to raise my lashes from the root as much as I can.
I'm not doing eyelash perms or anything like that.
I don't do eyelash perms or anything like that.
I don't do eyelash perms, so I think it's best to use a dry eyelash curler.
I think it's really good to use the curler when your eyelashes are dry.
Then there's no moisture in the lashes.
So it's very easy to raise the lashes.
The holding power is great, so it might not be so good.
I don't know if this is a good idea.
But if you use a hair dryer
It might not be so good, but if you give it a light breeze with a hair dryer or something
It might make the lashes come up a little easier.
I'm going to apply this primer.
But honestly, I don't care what kind of primer you use.
I just want them to go up, up, up.
I'm going to use a hot brower later.
I'll use a hot brower later.
Don't worry too much at this time.
I'm going to paint the lower lashes in the same way.
I'd like to draw an eyeliner.
First of all, use this. First of all, you need to use this.
Many of our members are using it a lot.
I didn't know this at first
I learned it from one of the members.
This is a very soft eyeliner.
Fill in the mucous membrane of the eye.
Usually, I don't take it out from this eyelash.
But today, I'm going to pull it out a little bit.
I'm just going to pull it out a little bit like this.
I'm going to use this thin brush that I used at the beginning.
I'm going to extend the eyeliner like this.
I'm going to extend it along the straight line of the eye like this.
Then it doesn't feel like I'm drawing.
It's like I'm saying, "My eyes are this big from the start.
It looks very natural.
I highly recommend this.
Next, I used a liquid eyeliner
Use a liquid eyeliner.
I don't want to bounce it up a little bit at the corner of the eye.
I'm going to draw it straight along the shape of the eye.
Apply mascara.
I use this mascara.
Even in everyday life, the impression of the eyelashes is very important.
I've been using it for quite a long time.
Slightly bunched lashes
I wanted to create a trendy bunchy look.
I use tweezers.
I used tweezers to attach the lashes to each other.It's like attaching the lashes to each other.
If you do this too much, the amount of lashes will decrease.
It tends to make the lashes thinner, so the key is to do it gently.
The key is to do it gently.
Next, I'd like to talk about blush.
I use this one.
It's a pretty color like strawberry.
Take a little bit of the darker part of the blush and mix it with the lighter part.
And mix in a little bit of the lighter part.
I put it on a tissue.
and wash it off with a smiley face.
My face is a little bit round for me, so
I'm going to put a little bit of it in from the outside.
I personally think it looks beautiful.
I think it looks better if I put it in at a slight angle like this.
The tip of the nose can also be done like this.
I think it makes it easier to blend in.
When the makeup is completed
It will look balanced when the makeup is completed.
The tip of the nose and the chin.
And a little bit on the chin.
It's okay if you can't tell if it's really there or not.
Then I'm going to apply lipstick first.
This is what I usually wear.
I got this as a birthday present from one of the members.
It's not a very dark color.
I mean...
I apply a little bit like this.
I blur it with my hand.
Yes, sir. Yes, ma'am.
And this is the last of my regular makeup.
I'm going to use this.
This is like a highlighter.
It makes me look really shiny.
I also use this for live performances.
I apply it under my eyes and on the highest part of my cheeks.
I apply it like this.
I think it depends on the bone structure of the face.
I think this is a great place to apply it.
I also apply a little bit to the tip of the nose.
Apply a little bit on the tip of the nose and also on the darkest part of the face.
So it looks like this.
Then I want to use a little bit of nose shadow to make the nose look shiny.
I'm going to take a brush and apply this as well.
Use the lightest color for this.
Just a little bit on the tip of the nose like this.
I can apply it like this.
I'm going to use the rest of the color and connect it to the top of the nose.
Then take a little bit of the darker part.
Put a little bit under the nose like this.
This completes the normal makeup for now.
Makeup for the live performance
I think the makeup will be a little darker.
It's not for a party or anything like that.
But when you go to a glamorous place...
I think it's not at all unnatural to do live makeup.
I don't think it's unnatural, so please try to imitate it.
Next, I'm going to try this one.
The second color from the end.Second color from the edge.
This is it.
I'm going to put this on my chest.
Put this on your chest again.
Blend it into a tissue and apply it to your chest.
Then apply it to the width of your shoulders.
This is skin color, so it doesn't go on too thick.
so it doesn't go on too thick.
It doesn't look unnatural even if it's too thick.
It doesn't look unnatural.
When I don't have time, I often apply it by hand.
I often apply it by hand when I don't have much time.
I apply it very clearly.
I apply the same color to the triangle below.
You see this triangle here?
You see this triangle?
That's where I'm going to paint.
I'm going to use the leftover color to paint all the way down to the tip.
Paint it on all the way to the tip of the eye.
Paint the corner of the eye like this.
Just like this.
I'm done with the wide area.
Then, use a thin brush to apply this
This glitter on the bottom.
I mixed the brown glitter with the matte brown on top.
I mix the brown glitter with the matte brown on top.
I'm going to mix the brown glitter with the matte brown on top to make the color.
The color I just mentioned is a little bit
A little reddish or
pinkish.It's pinkish.
There are some colors in it.
Even if you apply it too thickly
I don't feel like I'm applying it too thickly.
The one I just used.
It's the same one I used earlier.
It's the same one I used for the tear troughs.
I used this pencil to make the tear troughs more defined.
I'm going to use this pencil
I'm going to draw it a little bit thicker.
to the outer corner of the eye
By drawing it long
It makes the eyes look bigger.
But if you draw it too long
I feel like I'm making it up.
I want to make it look like I'm making it up.
I want the outer part to be a little thinner.
While adjusting
while blending with your finger.
Next, I'm going to use this.
This is
Just now...
It's similar to this one.
This is some kind of pink
It's a liquid type.
It's a type of liquid.
Just under the dark eye.
like this.
Apply it to the crease of the eyelashes
Apply it to the crease of your eyelashes. I'm going to paint it.
In
Then the position of the eyes will be lowered
It makes the eyes look fuller.
If you have trouble with long eyes, this is a good choice.
Apply lightly to the tear ducts under the black eyes.
This is so light that you may wonder if it's really on.
It's okay if it's thin.
Let's go to the eyeliner.
Eyeliner is the same as the one I used earlier.
I use liquid eyeliner.
When I do live shows, I tend to bounce my eyeliner up a little bit.
I just squint a little bit.
This one is just an extension of the eye, and I just swipe it on at the end.
I blur it a little bit later.
It's okay if you think you drew it too thick.
And then I'm going to add a little bit of this lash line.
I want to make it look natural, so I'm going to do the upper part of the eye as well.
I'm going to do a little bit above the eye as well.
I'm going to mix a little bit of this glitter with a little bit of this glitter.
It's just a little bit, but it's a lot.
I think this gives the eyes a three-dimensional look.
I'm going to put it on top of the glitter.
The thinner you make it, the better it looks.
There are times when I do this and times when I don't.
When I'm not in the mood for it, or when I'm not in the mood for it.
When I'm not in the mood, or when I feel like I'm going to do something crazy today
I use this stick.
I put lame on it.
I usually use these two types depending on my mood.I usually use these two types depending on my mood
I usually use these two types depending on my mood or how the makeup turns out.
But today I think there are too many browns and not enough whites.
I feel like there are too many browns and not enough whites.
I'm going to use this one today.
I'm just going to put it on the black eye first.
I'm going to put it roughly like this.
Then I'm going to blend it out with my finger, but before it dries, I'm going to put it back in with a little bit of a tap.
If you do it too early, the lame will be scattered in various places.
So I recommend blending it horizontally and vertically like this.
Now most of the eye makeup is done, but since I applied eye shadow on top, the mascara is probably a little powdery, so I'm going to add a layer of mascara.
The last one is blush. The first blush I applied is a light pink, so I'm going to use this blush.
I'm going to use this one.
Like a doll.
I took a little bit of this pink like this.
I'm going to take a little bit of this and apply it on a small area where the black eye meets the side of the nose like this.
Lastly, I'd like to introduce the lips.
I've recently started using this lipstick for live performances, and it really doesn't come off.
When I'm singing live, my lips rub against the microphone.
I've been having a lot of trouble with my lips falling off when I'm singing live, but since I found this lip gloss, it doesn't fall off at all.
Shake it out and apply it to the inside of your lips.
After blending it in, I blended it out with my hand.
Like this.
Then, at the very end, I applied it to the corner of my eyes.
I think I applied it to the corner of my eyes.
I'm going to take a little bit of this and put it on one more time.
This time, I introduced both daily makeup and live makeup at the same time.
I'm going to show you my daily makeup and live makeup at the same time.
I am particular about my daily makeup. I'm usually particular about my makeup.
First of all, I'm going to use this slightly beige color
The main point is to use this color that is a little bit beige.
For live performances, I add a little darker color to the usual makeup and tighten it up.
and tighten it up.
The lip color that doesn't fall off is something I've been exploring.
I'm still trying to figure out what to do.
I've tried so many different lip colors.
This is my favorite among all of them.
I'd like to encourage everyone to imitate it.
I think it's relatively easy to imitate for everyday makeup.
I hope you will try to imitate me by wearing the same lipstick with the same lipstick.
That's all!
This is Natsumi Nakayama from Ocha-no-Uma.
I, Kitahara, often spend time with Natsumi Nakayama.
I often see Natsumi Nakayama with her friends, but I've never had the chance to see how she does her makeup.
I'm very happy to see it again in the video.
I also love doing makeup so much.
I wish I could give a makeup lecture like this.
First of all, the makeup is one of the things I like about you.
I thought that Natsumi looked very matured in the video.
I've been watching you since you were a trainee member of Halo Pro.
I've been watching her since she was a trainee member of Halopro, so I was surprised to see how much she's grown.
Now that I think that Natsumi, who was such a tiny little girl, is so particular about her makeup and wears it every day at her live performances
I thought she has become a very thoughtful and beautiful woman.
Also, Momochan mentioned earlier...
Momochan mentioned it earlier.
I really like your makeup too.
Thank you very much.
I have an image that you try many different kinds of makeup. I've got an image of you trying out quite a few different genres of makeup.
I really want to see Momo-chan's make-up class too.
I was hoping I'd get to see it someday.
That's for sure!
That's all for Natsumi Nakayama's makeup lecture!
Amazing, amazing, amazing, that one lie is the end of everything!
Morning Musume。23すごいフィーバー
Down on Scio
Let's do our best tomorrow!
It's time to say goodbye to Apkami, brought to you by Shinobu no Maki Sora and Momo Kitahara!
Well, we've seen various videos this time again, but I, Kitahara, was left with a strong impression of Tsubaki Factory's "Freedom" choreography, and I'd like to say something about it, but I really like it.
I want to say that I really like this song, and I dance to it a lot at home.
Like I said before, a lot of the members dance to it, so I hope we can spread the word through sns and the like.
I like Natsumi Nakayama's makeup class, and she uses a lot of brushes.
I really like this project, so of course I'd like to see more makeup lessons from the other members, but I don't know if I want to see someone else's makeup lesson.
Of course I would like to see more makeup lectures by different members, but I was hoping to see someone doing someone else's makeup in the future.
I hope I can do it someday.
Upgami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
This time, upgami's partners were Neenu Maxora of Tsubaki Factory and Momo Kitahara of Ochanomimi.
Farewell!
Next time on Upgoddess: Risa Ogata, the making of the music video "Just Like Hobby" and
And the recording of "Juice Juice Bon Voyage", the miracle of the thought!
me